barkingirons.com 2019-07-08

# Terms – Barking Irons

Skip to content

#### TERMS AND CONDITIONS

If you shop for Barking Irons Ltd., merchandise and place your orders through www.barkingirons.com, any personal information that you may share with us (and with the business partners that help this site function or assist us in fulfilling your order) is kept absolutely private. Neither your name nor anything about you is sold or shared with any other non-affiliated company or agency. We do ask you for certain kinds of personal information in order to provide the services you request. This information includes:

Mailing List – When you create an account with Barking Irons Ltd., you will be given the option to be added to the Barking Irons Ltd., mailing list. 

Purchases – When you place an order, you will be asked to provide your credit card information. Barking Irons Ltd., does not, however, store your credit card information.

Additionally, several of our functions use cookies. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a website that is saved on your hard drive by your computer’s browser. The cookie holds information a site may need to personalize/enhance your experience and to gather website statistical data, such as which pages are visited, the internet provider’s domain name and the addresses of the sites visited immediately before coming to and immediately after leaving www.barkingirons.com. However, none of this information is associated with you as an individual. It is measured anonymously and only in the aggregate. The information in the cookies lets Barking Irons Ltd., trace your “clickstream” activity (i.e., the paths taken by visitors to our site as they move from page to page) to enable us to better serve our customers by revealing which portions of our site are the most popular. Cookies contain absolutely no personal information. You may disable cookies on your browser. Please review your browser’s instructions for doing so.

#### YOUR SECURITY

Barking Irons Ltd., goes to great lengths to keep your financial information private and safe. We use Secure Socket Layers (SSL), the industry standard in transferring information to process your orders. The SSL encrypts, or translates, your order information into highly indecipherable code, which is processed immediately. All credit card transactions occur in a secure area of our site, to protect you from any loss, misuse or alteration of information collected. When you have finished shopping and begin the checkout process, you will move into the secure area of our site. Once you’ve entered, the page address (URL) will change from http to https, to let you know you are in a secure area. Also, a key or a closed lock will appear in the lower right hand corner of your screen to notify you of this change. You will remain in the secure zone for the entire checkout process. You acknowledge, however, that no transmission of data over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, despite our best efforts. Thus, while we will use every means possible to ensure the security of information you transmit to us, we cannot guarantee that such information will not be intercepted by third parties.

#### SPOOFING AND PHISHING

A common internet scam is known as spoofing or phishing. This occurs when you receive and email from what appears to be a legitimate source requesting personal information from you. Please be aware that Barking Irons Ltd., will never send you an email requesting you to verify credit card information, bank information, or any other personal information. If you ever receive and email that appears to be from us requesting such information from you, please DO NOT respond to it, and DO NOT click on any links appearing in the email. Instead, please forward the email to us at info@barkingirons.com, as we will investigate all instances of internet fraud.

#### CHILDREN

Our web site is not meant for children, and we will not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 without verified parental consent. We will remove from our files any personally identifiable information of anyone we discover to be under the age of 13.

#### YOUR CONSENT

You acknowledge that this privacy policy is part of the terms and service, and you agree that using this site signifies your assent to the Barking Irons Ltd.., Privacy Policy. Barking Irons Ltd., reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time without advanced notice. If the Barking Irons Ltd., Privacy Policy is changed, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information is collected, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

If you have any questions about your privacy or security at www.barkingirons.com, please call us at 212-226-1126 or email us at mail@barkingirons.com and include your name and the address in the message.

In order to ship and track merchandise, we make your name and address available to such companies and United Parcel Service and Federal Express. In no instances are these business affiliates allowed to use your personal information for any other purpose aside from shipping.

To be removed from our mailing list, please email us at MAIL@BARKINGIRONS.COM, and include your name and the address in the message.

#### PRIVACY POLICY

If you shop for Barking Irons Ltd., merchandise and place your orders through www.barkingirons.com, any personal information that you may share with us (and with the business partners that help this site function or assist us in fulfilling your order) is kept absolutely private. Neither your name nor anything about you is sold or shared with any other non-affiliated company or agency. We do ask you for certain kinds of personal information in order to provide the services you request. This information includes:

My account – You have the opportunity to create a personal shopping account with Barking Irons Ltd. This account will allow you to shop faster and easier and to check on order status and history. In creating this account, you authorize Barking Irons, Ltd., to store your name, e-mail address, telephone number, shipping and billing addresses. This is for your convenience only. The information is not used for any other purpose.

Mailing List – When you create an account with Barking Irons Ltd., you will be given the option to be added to the Barking Irons Ltd., mailing list. Whether or not you select this option, your personal information will never be shared with or sold to anyone. Additionally, subscriptions to the mailing list can be cancelled at any time.

Purchases – When you place an order, you will be asked to provide your credit card information. Barking Irons Ltd., does not, however, store your credit card information.

Additionally, several of our functions use cookies. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a website that is saved on your hard drive by your computer’s browser. The cookie holds information a site may need to personalize/enhance your experience and to gather website statistical data, such as which pages are visited, the internet provider’s domain name and the addresses of the sites visited immediately before coming to and immediately after leaving www.barkingirons.com. However, none of this information is associated with you as an individual. It is measured anonymously and only in the aggregate. The information in the cookies lets Barking Irons Ltd., trace your “clickstream” activity (i.e., the paths taken by visitors to our site as they move from page to page) to enable us to better serve our customers by revealing which portions of our site are the most popular. Cookies contain absolutely no personal information. You may disable cookies on your browser. Please review your browser’s instructions for doing so.

Opt out of ads using Digital Advertising Alliance  
Digital Advertising Alliance allows you to opt out of several ad tracking cookies placed by major social media sites and other ad tracking services. For instance, social media sites like Facebook uses tracking cookies to analyze your online behavior and show you ads tailored to your interests. Digital Advertising Alliance enables you to delete such ad tracking cookies placed by sites like Facebook.
